<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
<string name="eula" formatted="false">
\nCopyright© VenomVendor\n

\n
*** END USER LICENSE AGREEMENT ***
\n

\n
IMPORTANT: PLEASE READ THIS LICENSE CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS SOFTWARE.
\n

\n1. LICENSE\n

\n
By receiving, opening the file package, and/or using Deduplicate SMS("Software") containing this software, you agree that this End User License Agreement(EULA) is a legally binding and valid contract and agree to be bound by it. You agree to abide by the intellectual property laws and all of the terms and conditions of this Agreement.
\n

\n2. USER AGREEMENT\n

\n2.1 Use Restrictions\n

\n
You shall use Deduplicate SMS in compliance with all applicable laws and not for any unlawful purpose.
\n

\n2.2 Copyright Restriction\n

\n
This Software contains copyrighted material, trade secrets and other proprietary material. You shall not, and shall not attempt to, modify, reverse engineer, disassemble or decompile Deduplicate SMS. Nor can you create any derivative works or other works that are based upon or derived from Deduplicate SMS in whole or in part.
\n

\n2.3 Limitation of Responsibility\n

\n
You will indemnify, hold harmless, and defend VenomVendor against any and all claims, proceedings, demand and costs resulting from or in any way connected with your use of VenomVendor\'s Software.
\n

\n
In no event (including, without limitation, in the event of negligence) will VenomVendor be liable for any consequential, incidental, indirect, special or punitive damages.
\n

\n2.5 Warranties\n

\n
THIS APP COMES WITH NO WARRANTY
\n

\n2.6 Governing Law\n

\n
This Agreement shall be governed by the law of the India applicable therein. You hereby irrevocably attorn and submit to the non-exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of India therefrom. If any provision shall be considered unlawful, void or otherwise unenforceable, then that provision shall be deemed severable from this License and not affect the validity and enforceability of any other provisions.
\n

\n2.7 Termination\n

\n
Any failure to comply with the terms and conditions of this Agreement will result in automatic and immediate termination of this license.\n

\n3. DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTY\n

\n
THIS SOFTWARE AND THE ACCOMPANYING FILES ARE SOLD "AS IS" AND WITHOUT WARRANTIES AS TO PERFORMANCE OR MERCHANTABILITY OR ANY OTHER WARRANTIES WHETHER EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED. THIS DISCLAIMER CONCERNS ALL FILES GENERATED AND EDITED BY Deduplicate SMS AS WELL.
\n

\n4. CONSENT OF USE OF DATA\n
\n
No data is collected.
\n</string>
</resources>
